ignitermedia.com 2011-12-22

# Privacy Policy | Igniter Media

Igniter Media (IM) is committed to maintaining your trust and confidence. The following online privacy policy is intended to protect and secure the personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified) you provide to our organization online.

Click one of the links below to jump to that section:

  * Awareness
  * Information We Collect
  * How the Information is Used
  * Sharing of Personal Information
  * Security
  * Cookies
  * Children's Online Privacy
  * Links to Outside Sites
  * Removal From our Mailing List
  * Contacting Us

## Awareness

IM provides this online privacy policy to inform you of the way your information is collected and used as well as to make you aware of our security practices. We also provide you with the opportunity to remove your name from our postal mailing list, if you desire to do so. 

## Information We Collect

There are two different ways in which we collect information from visitors on our Web site:

1\. From online requests for information (i.e. e-mail newsletters, contact forms, etc.);

2\. From online requests for materials from our organization (i.e. requesting a free offer)

The information we collect online includes name, address, city, state, ZIP/postal code, telephone number, e-mail address, and, in the case of online shopping, credit card number and expiration date. In order to continuously improve our service to you and tailor our future communications to you, we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your demographics, comments, professional interests, and contact preferences.

## How the Information is Used

IM uses your information to understand your needs and provide you with better online service. We may use your information to complete a transaction, to update you on our projects and videos, or to personalize our Web site for you. Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for any other purposes. We also provide you the opportunity to remove your name from our postal mailing list, if you desire to do so. Please review the corresponding section of this privacy policy below.

In addition, IM will not send you e-mail that you have not agreed to receive. We may periodically send you e-mail announcing news and event information. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, you may receive mailings from us as well.

## Sharing of Personal Information

IM never sells, rents, leases or exchanges your personal information with other organizations. IM assures you that the identity of all who contact us through this Web site will be kept confidential. IM may occasionally send mailings on behalf of other organizations or ministries when their interests align with IM. Use of your personal information will be limited to further the ministry activities of IM and partner ministries.

## Security

IM is committed to ensuring the security of your personal information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the proper use of information, we have established and implemented appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. IM uses Internet Encryption Software, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) Protocol when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. Any information you enter is encrypted at your browser, sent over the public Internet in encrypted form, and then de-encrypted at our server. Once we receive your credit card information, it is accessible only to a small number of trusted IM employees who have been specially trained in processing this information.

## Cookies

From time to time, we may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard drive or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to recognize you when you return to our sites, or to identify which areas of our network of Web sites you have visited. We may use this information to better personalize the content you see on our sites.

Many Web sites place cookies on your hard drive. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. Your browser can refuse all cookies, or show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

## Children's Online Privacy

We are concerned about the privacy of young children and do not knowingly collect any personal information from a child under 13. We encourage you to become involved with your child's access to the Internet and to our site in order to ensure that his or her privacy is well protected.

To read more about online safety and how to become more involved with your child's online experience, visit the Federal Trade Commission Web site. You may also benefit from the information and resources available on [ProtectKids.com](http://www.protectkids.com/).

## Links to Outside Sites

This Web site links to documents located on Web sites maintained by other organizations or individuals. Once you access a link to another Web site, please be aware that IM is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Removal from Our Mailing List

We give you the opportunity to remove your name from our postal mailing list so that you do not receive any future communications from our ministry. If you desire to permanently remove your name, you can contact customer service. If you determine that our information about you is inaccurate or it has changed, you may also modify information by contacting customer service.

## Contacting Us

If you have comments or questions about our online privacy policy, or would like more information about IM, or are experiencing technical trouble, please contact us.
